{
   "questions_4_Option":[
      {
         "question":"My computer is not ______ of running this software.",
         "answer1":"able",
         "answer2":"compatible",
         "answer3":"capable",
         "answer4":"suitable",
         "correct":"capable"
      },
      {
         "question":"It's said that he has ______ friends of his age.",
         "answer1":"few",
         "answer2":"plenty",
         "answer3":"a little",
         "answer4":"little",
         "correct":"few"
      },
      {
         "question":"The students ______ to be at school at 3 p.m.",
         "answer1":"told",
         "answer2":"have told",
         "answer3":"were told",
         "answer4":"tell",
         "correct":"were told"
      },
      {
         "question":"He bought all the books ______ are needed for the English course.",
         "answer1":"that",
         "answer2":"who",
         "answer3":"what",
         "answer4":"those",
         "correct":"that"
      },
      {
         "question":"The shirt in the window was ______ expensive for me to buy.",
         "answer1":"too",
         "answer2":"such",
         "answer3":"enough",
         "answer4":"so",
         "correct":"too"
      },
      {
         "question":"He couldn't get back _____ his car. He had locked himself out.",
         "answer1":"on",
         "answer2":"into",
         "answer3":"in",
         "answer4":"to",
         "correct":"into"
      },
      {
         "question":"Every member in Nataly's class admires her ______.",
         "answer1":"honesty",
         "answer2":"dishonest",
         "answer3":"dishonesty",
         "answer4":"honest",
         "correct":"honesty"
      },
      {
         "question":" If I were in charge, I ______ things differently.",
         "answer1":"will do",
         "answer2":"would do",
         "answer3":"would have done",
         "answer4":"had done",
         "correct":"would do"
      },
      {
         "question":"He is going to get married ______ the end of this month.",
         "answer1":"on",
         "answer2":"in",
         "answer3":"to",
         "answer4":"at",
         "correct":"in"
      },
      {
         "question":"Just think, ______ 2 years' time, we'll be 20 both.",
         "answer1":"under",
         "answer2":"in",
         "answer3":"after",
         "answer4":"over",
         "correct":"in"
      },
      {
         "question":"The room needs ______ for the wedding.",
         "answer1":"decorating",
         "answer2":"to decorate",
         "answer3":"decorate",
         "answer4":"be decorated",
         "correct":"decorating"
      },
      {
         "question":"I'm afraid I'm not really ______ to comment on this matter.",
         "answer1":"qualifying",
         "answer2":"qualified",
         "answer3":"quality",
         "answer4":"qualitative",
         "correct":"qualified"
      },
      {
         "question":"How long does the play ______?",
         "answer1":"last",
         "answer2":"extend",
         "answer3":"prolong",
         "answer4":"stretch",
         "correct":"last"
      }
   ],
   "questions_True_False": [
      {
         "question":"President Ho Chi Minh was born on May 19, 1890 in Kim Lien town.",
         "answer2":"Correct",
         "answer3":"Wrong",
         "correct":"Correct"
      },
      {
         "question":"General Vo Nguyen Giap was promoted to military rank in 1948.",
         "answer2":"Correct",
         "answer3":"Wrong",
         "correct":"Correct"
      },
      {
         "question":"Vietnamese people do not like to eat bread for breakfast.",
         "answer2":"Correct",
         "answer3":"Wrong",
         "correct":"Wrong"
      },
      {
         "question":"The French agreed to sign the Gionevo agreement because they lost to the Vietnamese at the battle of Dien Bien Phu.",
         "answer2":"Correct",
         "answer3":"Wrong",
         "correct":"Correct"
      },
      {
         "question":"VietNam U23 team has won the Seagame Championship twice.",
         "answer2":"Correct",
         "answer3":"Wrong",
         "correct":"Wrong"
      },
      {
         "question":"Cristiano Ronaldo never wanted to go to VietNam.",
         "answer2":"Correct",
         "answer3":"Wrong",
         "correct":"Wrong"
      },
      {
         "question":"April 30 and May 1 are the days when Vietnam unifies the North and South.",
         "answer2":"Correct",
         "answer3":"Wrong",
         "correct":"Correct"
      }
   ]
}